trac.jobs 2017-12-31

# trac.jobs

## TRAC SYSTEMS LIMITED

## Privacy Policy

Trac Systems Limited is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to www.healthjobsuk.com. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

By using, registering or submitting any information on our Site you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this Privacy Policy.

1\. Definitions

1.1 The following words and expressions have the following meanings unless inconsistent with the context:

"Compliance Officer"

| 

Simon Headington, Trac Systems Limited, PO Box 8, Bakewell, Derbyshire, DE45 1YG, info@healthjobsuk.com;  
  
---|---  
  
"cookies"

| 

a small amount of data sent from the server, which is then stored on your computer's hard disc drive;  
  
"DPA"

| 

Data Protection Act 1998 as amended;  
  
"data processors"

"personal data"

"process" or "processing"

"sensitive personal data"

| 

}  
}  
}  
}

| 

as defined in the DPA;  
  
"Site"

| 

www.healthjobsuk.com;  
  
"we", "us" or "our"

| 

Trac Systems Limited a company registered in England and Wales with company number 04028397 whose registered office is at Heath Bank, Main Street, Great Longstone, Bakewell, Derbyshire, DE45 1TA; and  
  
"you", "your"

| 

an individual, company, or firm accessing our Site.  
  
2\. Introduction

2.1 This Privacy Policy is a statement as to how we shall process your personal data. We take the security and privacy of you and your personal data very seriously and we are committed to safeguarding your privacy on line. Please be aware that communications over the internet, such as emails, are not secure unless they are encrypted. We do not accept any responsibility for any unauthorised access or loss of personal data beyond our control. You may access most areas of our Site without registering with us. Certain areas of our Site are only open to you if you register.

2.2 Our primary reasons for collecting your personal data are to:

2.2.1 provide you with e-mail alerts in respect of jobs falling within your specified criteria if requested by you;

2.2.2 provide your details to employers and/or recruitment agencies for the purposes of obtaining application packs for jobs if requested to do so by you;

2.2.3 process on-line applications, any other documents and any responses to pre-application questions you may submit on the Site; and

2.2.4 provide you with the most efficient service possible.

2.3 This Privacy Policy may change from time to time so please check it periodically.

2.4 Our Site contains links to other websites. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites and advise you to read the privacy statements of each website you visit which collects personal information.

3\. Our Policy for Processing your Personal Data

3.1 What personal data do we process and where do we get it from?

3.1.1 When you register on our Site we will collect personal data from you.

3.1.2 When you request an application pack on the Site we may collect personal data from you.

3.1.3 When you complete an on-line application form, submit any document or respond to any pre application questions on the Site we will collect personal data from you.

3.1.4 Personal information may also be obtained automatically by your internet browser.

3.1.5 The types of personal data which we may collect from you could include, for example, your name, your contact details (such as your address and email address from you) and other information collected from you when registering to use the Site or when submitting an on-line application form, other document or answers to any pre-application questions on our Site.

3.1.6 We may also collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to our Site through the use of cookies. This information may include, for example, the pages which you browse. This information helps us to better manage and develop our Site.

4\. What do we do with your Personal Data?

4.1 We will process your personal data so that:

4.1.1 we can, if requested, provide you with email alerts for jobs falling within your specified criteria;

4.1.2 we can process any application forms, other documents or answers to pre-application questions submitted by you on our Site on behalf of relevant employers in accordance with their recruitment processes;

4.1.3 we can provide your contact details to employers and/or recruitment agencies for the provision of application packs by the employer and/or recruitment agency directly to you if requested by you. This may include transferring your contact details, but no other personal data, outside the EEA if the employer and/or recruitment agency is based outside the EEA;

4.1.4 we can deal with the general queries you raise from time to time, by post, by email, by fax or by telephone; and

4.1.5 we can process your registration details.

4.2 Other purposes for which we may process your personal data are:

4.2.1 the general administration of your records by us;

4.2.2 the general maintenance of our database and records by us including maintaining copies of any application submitted by you on the Site in accordance with the relevant employer's recruitment policy;

4.2.3 for security purposes to protect your personal data held and/or processed by us;

4.2.4 for training our employees in respect of providing our service to you; and

4.2.5 where you agree for our general marketing purposes; and

4.2.6 to send you e-mails from carefully selected companies who provide services which we think may be of interest to you where you have notified us that you are happy for us to use your personal data in this manner.

4.3 When you enter our Site, your computer will automatically be issued with a cookie. Cookies in themselves do not identify the individual user, just the computer used. Many websites do this whenever a user visits their website in order to track traffic flows. If you wish to reject our cookie, you can configure your browser to do so (see Condition 10 below), alternatively you can ask your internet browser to alert you when a cookie is being set up. If you disable our Cookie you may find that you are unable to access certain features on the Site or that certain features, such as online application forms, may not operate correctly.

4.4 You acknowledge that by providing personal data to us, you consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy _._

5\. Who else gets to see your Personal Data?

5.1 Our data processors.

5.2 Any third party employers and/or recruitment agencies advertising a job on our Site in respect of which you submit an on-line application, other document or answer pre-application questions on our Site or in respect of which you submit a request an application pack.

6\. Your Rights

6.1 You have the right to object to your personal data being used for 'direct marketing' and/or 'host mailing' purposes (see Conditions 4.2.5, and 4.2.6 above). You can change your options in relation to the information you wish to receive at any time by clicking the "unsubscribe link" on any email we send to you, updating your account details on the Site or by contacting our Compliance Officer in writing by post or email.

6.2 As mentioned above you can set your internet browser to refuse cookies or you can ask your internet browser to alert you when a cookie is being set up (see Condition 10).

6.3 You have the right under the DPA to request from us information as to what personal data we are processing about you. Such requests should be made in writing by post or email to the Compliance Officer and should be accompanied by a £10.00 fee. We will provide you with the relevant information within 40 days of receipt of the fee.

6.4 You have other rights under the DPA in relation to our processing of your personal data.

7\. Maintenance of your personal data

7.1 We are committed to the security of your personal data. All of our employees and sub-contractors with access to your personal data and/or who are associated with the processing of that data are contractually obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal data.

7.2 We have implemented technology measures and security policies to protect the personal data that we have in our control from unauthorised access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction or accidental loss.

8\. General application of our Privacy Policy

8.1 This Privacy Policy only applies to the collection and use of your personal data provided to us and not to personal data you may provide directly to third parties (including but without limitation to the operators of third party websites linked to our Site, or any application form submitted by you directly to the relevant employer and/or recruitment agency). Any third parties will have their own policies in respect of processing personal data you provide to them and/or your personal data that we may disclose to them in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

9\. Contact information

9.1 If you have any queries about our processing or use of your personal data you should write, in the first instance to our Compliance Officer.

9.2 If you want to learn more about your rights regarding your personal data, you should contact the Information Commissioner's office information line on: (0044) 01625 545745 or visit their website at [ www.ico.gov.uk ](http://www.ico.gov.uk/) .

10\. Cookies

10.1 Information on how to block cookies can normally be found within the help features of your browser. Information can also be found on the main browser websites:

[ http://www.microsoft.com](http://www.microsoft.com/) (Internet Explorer)

[ http://www.opera.com](http://www.opera.com/) (Opera)

[ http://www.mozilla.org](http://www.mozilla.org/) (Firefox)
